KAROLINA JEDRZEJAK Software Developer

CONTACT

phone: 778 776 1417
LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/kjedrzejak/
e-mail: kjedrzejak91@gmail.com
website: https://k-jedrzejak.github.io/portfolio/

location: 102 Ave, Maple Ridge, BC, Canada

PROFILE

Software Developer with over five years of experience, specializing in building web applications using React.js and Vue.js. Consistently delivers improved performance and user satisfaction, while continually enhancing skills to stay current with industry trends and technologies.

SKILLS

Soft: Teamwork, Adaptability, Problem-solving, Critical thinking, Communication, Creativity, Time management, Attention to detail, Eagerness to learn, Emotional Intelligence

Technical: Programming: JavaScript, TypeScript, Vue.js, React.js, Next.js, Python, PHP / Styling: CSS3 (Less/Sass) / State Management: Redux, Context API / Database: NoSQL & SQL Databases / Testing: Jest.js / APIs: REST API, Ajax / Development Tools: Babel, Webpack, NPM, Yarn / Web Design: Responsive Web Design, Cross-Browser Compatibility / Design Tools: Photoshop, Figma / Methodologies: Agile

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Developer

CE Solutions, Hinton, Canada

08/2023 - 06/2024

- Developed web applications inluding logistics management platforms using Vue.js, React.js and C#.
- Created mobile applications for these platforms using Flutter.
- Developed a Python Programs for files management and database upload.
- Optimized database queries and REST API calls, boosting performance by about 40% and executed Jest.js unit tests.
- Led critical project enhancements, optimizing code for a 30% performance boost and improving user experience.
- Spearheaded UI/UX design and implemented new functionalities to enhance application responsiveness and efficiency.

JavaScript Developer

12/2022 - 08/2023

Adrino Mobile, Warsaw, Poland

- Developed engaging mobile ads featuring mini-games using JavaScript, TypeScript, and CSS3, resulting in a 60% increase in campaign revenue compared to static ads.
- Led frontend development for a platform overseeing publishers and advertisements, employing TypeScript, React.js, and Next.js.

- Managed tasks for the frontend development team, collaborated closely with the backend team to ensure seamless integration.
- Conducted thorough code reviews and provided feedback to the team to maintain high standards of code quality.
- Introduced TypeScript in advertising projects, speeding up development by 50%.

Magento2 Frontend Developer

02/2021 - 12/2022

Aurora Creation, Bialystok, Poland

- Developed Progressive Web Applications using React.js integrated with the Magento 2 platform for European brands, ensuring high performance on both mobile and desktop.
- Led 35% of the company's projects as Head Frontend Developer: managed tasks for a 3-person team, cooperated with clients and project managers by conducting project meetings.
- Served as the head full-stack developer for the website project at Mayko SEO Agency, spearheading all aspects from inception to completion independently, leveraging JavaScript and PHP.
- Implemented Magento2 training programs and conducted code reviews to ensure clean and efficient code.
- Collaborated with Cross-Functional Teams within an Agile framework, participating in daily stand-ups, sprint planning, and retrospective meetings. Maintained regular communication with design and backend teams, ensuring alignment on project objectives and timelines.
- Performed backend tasks reduced the backend team's workload by 15%, which accelerated project completion timelines.

Frontend Developer

08/2019 - 02/2021

Euro-Net, Warsaw, Poland

- Implemented promotional product landing pages with JavaScript, CSS3, and FreeMarker boosted online sales by approximately 40% and traffic to manufacturers' direct websites.
- Collaborated closely with graphic designers and the marketing department to finalize Landing Page specifications.
- Worked with backend developers on the company's main portals.

Junior Frontend Developer

03/2019 - 08/2019

Praca.pl, Warsaw, Poland

- Developed custom landing pages using JavaScript, PHP and CSS3 integrated with job offers from the main portal.
- Achieved a notable increase of approximately 500 daily users on the praca.pl homepage due to the impact of SEO-optimized landing pages.

EDUCATION

Computer Science

10/2017 - 07/2019

Bialystok Technical University, Bialystok, Poland

· Completed 2 years of a 3.5-year program

Management and Production Engineering

Bialystok Technical University, Bialystok, Poland

· Bachelor's degree

10/2010 - 04/2014